Guide to the Records and Papers of Terry Sanford, 1945-1998 UA.03.60.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Series 3. Political Papers, 1965-1976
  - Subseries 3.1. Personal and Political Papers, 1954-1985.
    - United Campus Ministry, 1971- (Box 176)
    - Joint Center for Federal and Regional Studies (Box 176)
    - Requests for photographs, autographs (Box 176)
    - Oversized personal (Box 177)
      - Expense reports (Box 177)
      - Clippings (Box 177)
      - Speeches by Sen. W. Kerr Scott, 1955-1958 (Box 177)
      - Appreciation Dinner, financial records, 1967 (Box 177)
    - Audiovisual Materials
      - Chet Huntley talks about North Carolina (NBC) Broadcast on WPTF-Raleigh, 1965 22 September (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0025)
        Conditions Governing Access
        Use of audiotapes and videotapes from this collection requires the creation of reference copies.
      - Durham Jaycee Celebrity Roast: Terry Sanford, 1981 March 17 (Box 182, Video-cassette UA03600001-Bcam-0001)
      - Hon. Terry Sanford speaks to CKEA, Richmond, Ky. (EKSC), 1965 24 September (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0008)
      - Institute on State Programming for the 1970s Reel #3: 9-12am Wednesday, 1967 February 15 (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0009)
      - Institute on State Programming for the 1970s Reel #4: 9-12am Wednesday, 1967 February 15 (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0009)
      - Institute on State Programming for the 1970s Reel #5: 2-5pm Wednesday, 1967 February 15 (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0009)
      - Institute on State Programming for the 1970s Reel #6: 2-5pm Wednesday, 1967 February 15 (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0009)
      - Nancy Hanks Memorial, 1983 February 25 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0168)
      - Newsmaker: Terry Sanford, 1967 11 November (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0010)
      - Political Science conference: Quail Roost Reel 1, 1965 28-29 May (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0006)
      - Political Science conference: Quail Roost Reel 2, 1965 28-29 May (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0007)
      - Presidential campaign announcement, 1972 8 March (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0012)
      - Primary night at Terry Sanford headquarters, 1972 6 May (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0013)
      - Quail Roose Conference on Institutes Tape 1, 1966 October 31 (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0014)
      - Quail Roose Conference on Institutes Tape 1, 1966 October 31 (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0015)
      - Quail Roose Conference on Institutes Tape 3, 1966 October 31 (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0016)
      - Sanford Appreciation Dinner Reel 1, 1964 4 December (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0003)
      - Sanford Appreciation Dinner Reel 2, 1964 4 December (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0004)
      - Sanford Appreciation Dinner Reel 3, 1964 4 December (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0005)
      - Sanford Inauguration (edited) Reel 1, 1961 5 January (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0001)
      - Sanford Inauguration (edited) Reel 3, 1961 5 January (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0002)
      - Testimonial Dinner Honoring Professor Joseph J. Spengler, 1972 January 14 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0169)
      - Three Little Maids from School Are We etc., 1970 29 May (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0011)
      - #1 Thursday pm (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0017)
      - #2 Thursday afternoon/evening (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0018)
      - #3 Thursday evening (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0019)
      - #4 Friday am (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0020)
      - #5 Friday am (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0021)
      - #6 Friday pm (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0022)
      - #7 Friday pm (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0023)
      - #8 Friday pm and Saturday am (Box 178, Audio-reel UA03600001-RR-0024)
  - Subseries 3.2: 1972 Presidential Campaign, 1961-1974
    Correspondence, memoranda, clippings, film, speeches, statements, drafts, press releases, and printed matter documenting Terry Sanford's campaigns for the Democratic nomination for President in 1972. The 1972 Campaign records include subjects and correspondents such as Civil Rights, Busing, the Democratic National Convention, Hubert Humphrey, Edmund Muskie, Richard Nixon, and George Wallace. Position files consist of speeches and statements illustrating Sanford's opinions on such issues as education, foreign policy, and tax reform. State files include correspondence, clippings, and information about campaigning in those states.
    - Bennett, Bert, 1962-1972 (Box 195)
    - Beyle, Thad, 1972 (Box 195)
    - Blacks: Civil Rights, 1967-1973 (Box 195)
    - Bowles, Hargrove (Skipper), 1971-1972 (Box 195)
    - Busing, 12972 (Box 195)
    - Carter, Hodding: Nomination of Sanford in Miami, 1972 (Box 195)
    - Clippings, 1972 (Box 195)
    - Clippings, 1972 (Box 195)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1965-1972 (Box 195)
    - Democratic National Convention Miami, Florida, 1972 (Box 195)
    - Democratic Study Group (U.S. House of Representatives), 1969 (Box 195)
    - Economy, 1975 (Box 195)
    - Elections, cost, 1971; 1974 (Box 195)
    - Electoral College, 1965-1967 (Box 195)
    - Ellington, Pete, 1971 (Box 195)
    - Harper, Margaret, 1972 (Box 195)
    - Harris, Fred, 1971 (Box 195)
    - Hoving, John, 1970-1972 (Box 195)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1971-1972 (Box 195)
    - Hunt, James B., 1971-1972 (Box 195)
    - Issues, 1972 (Box 196)
    - Johnson, Ralph, undated (Box 196)
    - Jordan, B. Everett, 1970-1972 (Box 196)
    - Keys, 1972 (Box 196)
    - McKay, Martha, 1971 (Box 196)
    - McGovern, George, 1971-1972 (Box 196)
    - Mills, Wilbur, 1971-1972 (Box 196)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1972; 2 folders (Box 196)
    - Miscellaneous: memorandums, notes, and correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 196)
    - Miscellaneous newsclippings, 1971-1972 (Box 196)
    - Miscellaneous: statements, 1972; undated (Box 196)
    - Miscellaneous: Youth for Sanford, 1972; undated (Box 196)
    - Morton, Hugh, 1971 (Box 196)
    - Muskie, Ed, 1971-1972 (Box 197)
    - Neat thoughts, 1966; undated (Box 197)
    - Nixon, Richard, undated (Box 197)
    - Nominating Speeches for Sanford, Miami, 1972; 2 folders (Box 197)
    - Photos: prints and contact sheets, 1972 (Box 197)
    - Photos: Campaign extras and not utilized (slides) (1/3), 1972 (Box 197)
    - Photos: Campaign extras and not utilized (slides) (2/3), 1972 (Box 197)
    - Photos: Campaign extras and not utilized (slides) (3/3), 1972 (Box 197)
    - Promotional materials: Campaign buttons, 1972 (Box 255)
    - Promotional materials: flyers, brochures, mailings, 1972 (Box 197)
    - Promotional materials: press releases & statements, 1972 (Box 197)
    - Promotional materials: press release folders, 1972 (Box 197)
    - Promotional materials: press release folders, 1972; 2 folders (Box 198)
    - Research materials: Bipartisan Congressional Cleaning House, circa 1972 (Box 198)
    - Research materials: Presidential Nominating Procedures in 1964, 1965 (Box 198)
    - Research materials: A Survey of the Political Climate in North Carolina, 1971 (Box 198)
    - Sanford Student Petition, 1972 (Box 270)
    - Smith, Hulett, 1967; 4 folders (Box 198)
    - Speeches: Positions, 1970-1972; 2 folders (Box 199)
    - Speeches: Statements, Releases, 1970-1974 (Box 199)
    - Survey of Voter Opinion, April 15, 1972 (Box 270)
    - Survey of Voter Opinion and Electorate Breakdown in North Carolina vol. 1, 1972 April 15 (Box 202)
    - Survey of Voter Opinion and Electorate Breakdown in North Carolina vol. 2, 1972 April 15 (Box 203)
    - Taxes, circa 1972 (Box 200)
    - Taylor, Pat, 1971-1972 (Box 200)
    - Viet Nam, 1972; undated (Box 200)
    - Wallace, George, 1972 (Box 200)
    - Wilson, Henry Hall, dinner for, 22 May 1967 (Box 200)
    - Alabama, 1967-1972 (Box 200)
    - Alaska, 1972 (Box 200)
    - Arizona, 1968-1972 (Box 200)
    - Arkansas, 1967-1972 (Box 200)
    - California, 1967-1972 (Box 200)
    - Colorado, 1967-1972 (Box 200)
    - Connecticut, 1967-1972 (Box 201)
    - Delaware, 1967-1972; 2 folders (Box 201)
    - D.C., 1969-1972 (Box 201)
    - Florida, 1967-1972 (Box 201)
    - Georgia, 1967-1972 (Box 201)
    - Hawaii, 1972 (Box 201)
    - Idaho, 1967-1972 (Box 201)
    - Illinois, 1968-1972 (Box 201)
    - Indiana (delegates), 1972 (Box 204)
    - Kansas, 1967-1972 (Box 204)
    - Kentucky (delegates), 1965-1972 (Box 204)
    - Louisiana (political situation), 1968-1972 (Box 204)
    - Maine, 1966-1972 (Box 204)
    - Maryland, 1967-1972 (Box 204)
    - Massachusetts, 1966-1973 (Box 204)
    - Michigan, 1972 (Box 204)
    - Minnesota, 1967-1972 (Box 204)
    - Missouri, 1968-1972 (Box 204)
    - Mississippi, 1967-1972 (Box 204)
    - Montana, 1972 (Box 204)
    - Nebraska, 1972; 2 folders (Box 204)
    - New Jersey, 1968-1972 (Box 230)
    - New Mexico, 1966-1969; 2 folders (Box 230)
    - New York, 1965-1972; 2 folders (Box 230)
    - North Carolina, 1965-1972 (Box 230)
    - North Dakota, 1967-1968; 1972 (Box 230)
    - Ohio, 1972 (Box 231)
    - Oklahoma, 1968-1972 (Box 231)
    - Oregon, 1972 (Box 231)
    - Pennsylvania, 1967-1972 (Box 231)
    - Rhode Island, 1967-1972 (Box 231)
    - South Carolina, 1967-1972 (Box 231)
    - South Dakota, 1972; 2 folders (Box 231)
    - Tennessee, 1967-1972 (Box 231)
    - Texas, 1967-1972 (Box 231)
    - Utah, 1965-1969 (Box 231)
    - Vermont, 1972; 3 folders (Box 231)
    - Virginia, 1967-1972 (Box 232)
    - Virgin Islands, 1972 (Box 232)
    - Washington, 1967-1972 (Box 232)
    - West Virginia, 1968-1972 (Box 232)
    - Wisconsin, 1968-1972 (Box 232)
    - Wyoming, 1967-1972 (Box 232)
    - Foreign Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 232)
  - Subseries 3.3. 1972 Presidential Campaign Films
    Includes audiovisual materials.
    This series contains the original film and sound recordings created by Drew Associates, a documentary film company, for campaign advertisements for Terry Sanford's 1972 Presidential campaign. Some notes on the exact format, contents, and codes to match motion picture and sound are included. Recordings include original raw footage as well as edited versions. The series also includes two videos created by Ralph Johnson Associates.
    The majority of the reels in this series were re-wound onto new reel cores for preservation during processing in 2017; labelings and marking have been recorded as the item's title but no attempt at arranging or matching picture to sound or varying versions has yet been made.
    - Drew Associates project binder, 1972 (Box 255)
    - Film can notes, 1972 (Box 255)
    - Sanford Interview, Sanford on Wallace, by Drew Associates, 1972 April 22 (Box 272, Video-reel UA03600001-Vid2-0002)
    - Sanford "Taxes" by Ralph Johnson Associates, 1972 April 24 (Box 272, Video-reel UA03600001-Vid2-0003)
    - Terry Sanford for President by Ralph Johnson Associates, Inc., 1972 April 26 (Video-reel UA03600001-Vid2-0001)
    - 24-264 A Wash Note labeled 1) Press conference?, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0001)
    - J121 19379-20169 Note labeled Sanford in Auto, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0002)
    - J225 70756-71549, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0003)
    - J121 20185-20977 Sanford Rolls 4, 7, 8, 13 1 Reel WO #DD702, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0004)
    - J121 24323-24922, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0005)
    - J129 56358-57136 Durham NC, Bebell #33557, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0006)
    - J231 31670-32403; 3985 DD-1 & 2 Bebell 33846 R1, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0007)
    - J229 21057-21632; 3985 Bebell 33846, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0008)
    - J121 21859-22654;Sanford Cam. AM 14-15-16 R 2 of 3 DD701, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0009)
    - J129 55509-56208 WO# DD-701 Reel 3 of 3 Sanford [?] 3-5-9, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0010)
    - J264 48776-49561, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0011)
    - J230 47978-48776, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0012)
    - J225 71602-72356 Note labeled 1972 campaign speech; Bebell 33846 Drew 3985 DD-1&2, 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0013)
    - J178 61802-62480 Note labeled 1972 campaign HQ; Drew Wash #24-265 A Head; Drew Associates: #18 #L-M Bebell #34225, 1972 April 12; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0014)
    - J293 31268-39666 Note labeled 1) Campaigning, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0015)
    - J238 48301-49089, 1972; 16mm (Box 256, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0016)
    - J228 35661-36460, 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0017)
    - J129 57964-58204, J233 88129-88331 Note labeled 1) Press conference, Hotel Sir Walter 2) Duke U. Scenes (Gardens), 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0018)
    - J265 76577-76754, J129 54270-54677 Note labeled 1) Sanford in auto 2) Sanford Day in Laurinburg, 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0019)
    - J257 53612-54295 Note labeled 1) Campaign rally (opening Durham HQ?), 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0020)
    - J265 74726-75113 Note labeled 1) Campaign ads 2) Campaign ad 1972 3) TS in Larinburg (?) 4) Campaign ad 1972; Sanford #81-C Washington Desk, 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0021)
    - J235 20057-20763 Note labeled Sanford Day in Laurinburg, 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0022)
    - J234 30045-30348, J264 47956-48149 Note labeled 1972 Campaign HQ 2) At TS Home, 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0023)
    - J259 31382-31610, J240 97319-97540 Note labeled 1) NCSL (1972) 2) At home of TS with students; Drew Assoc 3983 1A-1-2-3-4, 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0024)
    - J259 25743-26543, 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0025)
    - J238 97685-98466, 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0026)
    - J240 98137-98920, 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0027)
    - 246-0891 Drew Assoc. "Sanford for Pres." 16 [mag?] OK TKS #3, 5, 6, & 7; #81 work materials C, D, G, F, H; #81-C Wash. Desk 'A' TRK, TRK Rem. HD, 1972 April 25; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0028)
    - 246-0891 Drew Assoc. "Sanford for Pres." 16 [mag?] OK TKS #3, 5, 6, & 7; #81 work materials C, D, G, F, H; #81-D Wash. Desk 'A' TRK, TRK Rem. HD, 1972 April 25; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0029)
    - 246-0891 Drew Assoc. "Sanford for Pres." 16 [mag?] OK TKS #3, 5, 6, & 7; #81 work materials C, D, G, F, H; Tail Slop N.C. Hdqtrs. 30 sec. #81-F, 1972 April 25; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0030)
    - 246-0891 Drew Assoc. "Sanford for Pres." 16 [mag?] OK TKS #3, 5, 6, & 7; #81 work materials C, D, G, F, H; Tail Slop Students 30 seconds #81-H, 1972 April 25; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0031)
    - 246-0891 Drew Assoc. "Sanford for Pres." 16 [mag?] OK TKS #3, 5, 6, & 7; #81 work materials C, D, G, F, H; Tail Pix Wash. Desk #81-C, 1972 April 25; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0032)
    - 246-0891 Drew Assoc. "Sanford for Pres." 16 [mag?] OK TKS #3, 5, 6, & 7; #81 work materials C, D, G, F, H; 'B' TRK #81-C, 1972 April 25; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0033)
    - 246-0891 Drew Assoc. "Sanford for Pres." 16 [mag?] OK TKS #3, 5, 6, & 7; #81 work materials C, D, G, F, H; #81-D Wash. Press Pix, Pix Rem, 1972 April 25; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0034)
    - 246-0891 Drew Assoc. "Sanford for Pres." 16 [mag?] OK TKS #3, 5, 6, & 7; #81 work materials C, D, G, F, H; #81-C Wash. Desk, 1972 April 25; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0035)
    - 246-0891 Drew Assoc. "Sanford for Pres." 16 [mag?] OK TKS #3, 5, 6, & 7; #81 work materials C, D, G, F, H; #81-D Wash. Press Pix, 1972 April 25; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0036)
    - 246-0891 Drew Assoc. "Sanford for Pres." 16 [mag?] OK TKS #3, 5, 6, & 7; #81 work materials C, D, G, F, H; #81-G 1 min. Students Slop, 1972 April 25; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0037)
    - 2. NC Leadership (Pix and Trk) NC Leadership #81, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0038)
    - 2. NC Leadership (Pix and Trk) NC Leadership #81, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0039)
    - 3. NC Headquarters (Trk) NC Headquarters 1 min. #81, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0040)
    - 1. Inflation (Pix and Trk) Inflation #81, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0041)
    - 6. Plausibilities (Pix and Trk) Plausibilities #81, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0042)
    - 1. Inflation (Pix and Trk) Inflation #81, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0043)
    - 6. Plausibilities (Pix and Trk) Plausibilities #81, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0044)
    - 4. Mission (Pix and Trk) Mission #81, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0045)
    - 4. Mission (Pix and Trk) Mission #81, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0046)
    - 5. 'Durham' 5 minnute cut (Pix and Trk) Durham' 5 minute cut, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0047)
    - 7. Outs VA. 5 minute cut (Pix and Trk) Outs VA. 5 minutes, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0048)
    - 5. 'Durham' 5 minnute cut (Pix and Trk) Durham' 5 minute #81, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0049)
    - 7. Outs VA. 5 minute cut (Pix and Trk) Outs VA. 5 minute cut, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0050)
    - MOS AB-4 Sanford, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0051)
    - MOS BD-1 Sanford #81, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0052)
    - #81-I Sanford on Wallace 'C' Trk, 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0053)
    - #81-I 'Sanford Speaks on Wallace' 'B' Trk, 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0054)
    - #81-I 'A'-Trk Sanford on Wallace missing first piece: see can with original, 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0055)
    - Sanford for Pres work print color negative, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0056)
    - Sanford for Pres work print color print, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0057)
    - 246-0083 "Sanford for Pres" 16 mag mix E, F, G, H; trks 1-4, 1972 April 14; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0058)
    - 246-0628 "Sanford for Pres" 16 mag Tk# 1&2 #81-B (30 second comm.) Dummy Pix, 1972 March 27; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0059)
    - 246-0628 "Sanford for Pres" 16 mag Tk# 1&2 #81-A (one minute) Pix, 1972 March 27; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0060)
    - 246-0628 "Sanford for Pres" 16 mag Tk# 1&2 16 mag mix for #81-A: #81-B, 1972 March 27; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0061)
    - 246-0628 "Sanford for Pres" 16 mag Tk# 1&2 #81-A (1 min spot) all trks, 1972 March 27; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0062)
    - LM2 Reprint, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0063)
    - BD-Q, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0064)
    - Drew Associates #81 Sanford 15 minute cut, 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0065)
    - AB 6 Deveop only 7242 [??? EFB], 1972; 16mm (Box 259, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0066)
    - 16 maq mix #81 C-D, 1972; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0067)
    - cut 61, 1972; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0068)
    - #81 MOS 1 of 2 (scraps), 1972; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0069)
    - #81 MOS 2 of 2 (scraps), 1972; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0070)
    - Production #81 Film7242 ASA 250 Roll #11 Cameraman DD, [1972] May 06; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0071)
    - J238 96058-97130, 1972; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0072)
    - 246-0886 "Sanford Speaks on Wallace" 16 mag, TK #1, #81-I Work print, 1972 April 26; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0073)
    - 246-0886 "Sanford Speaks on Wallace" 16 mag, TK #1, #81-I Work print; 1/2 hour show, 1972 April 26; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0074)
    - 246-0886 "Sanford Speaks on Wallace" 16 mag, TK #1, #81-I Work print; scraps, 2 reels, 1972 April 26; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0075)
    - Production #81 Film7242 ASA 250 Roll #10 Cameraman DD, [1972] May 06; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0076)
    - J264 47956-48751, 1972; 16mm (Box 257, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0077)
    - J178 62484-63267, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0078)
    - Sanford AM 12-13-18, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0079)
    - W.S. at Duke U. BD GT, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0080)
    - AM 3 Reprint, 1972 March 18; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0081)
    - BD-Q sound reel, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0082)
    - BD-P sound reel, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0083)
    - R-1 straight transfers from cassette, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0084)
    - Washington Press Conference cassette, 1972 April 05; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0085)
    - R-2 straight transfers from cassette, 1972; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0086)
    - AM 7-8-13 Reprint, 1972; 16mm (Box 260, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0087)
    - AM 4 Reprint, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0088)
    - LM 1 Reprint, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0089)
    - #81-I NARR [O]UTS, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0090)
    - Bebell 34560 DD 6-7, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0091)
    - 15-min cut, 1972 April 03; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0092)
    - unknown fragment, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0093)
    - unknown fragments, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0094)
    - AM 5-9 Reprint, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0095)
    - AB 7-8-9-10-11-12, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0096)
    - #24-339, 1972 April 14; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0097)
    - J121 25128-25923 Sanford at Pres. House, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0098)
    - J287 25428-25620 Laurinberg, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0099)
    - Sanford primary 7242 DD 9, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0100)
    - #81-I Sanford on Wallace 'A' Trk, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0101)
    - #81-I original color cut, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0102)
    - #81-I mix track, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0103)
    - #81 E,F,G,H Work tracks: Students, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0104)
    - #81 E,F,G,H Work tracks: N.C. Headquarters, 1972; 16mm (Box 261, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0105)
    - soundtrack reel, 1972; 16mm (Box 262, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0106)
    - Drew Associates L-M 1-2 BD-L, 1972; 16mm (Box 262, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0107)
    - Tues. Night Correction BD-J, 1972; 16mm (Box 262, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0108)
    - Wed. AM Straight BD-J, 1972; 16mm (Box 262, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0109)
    - BD-J, 1972 March 30; 16mm (Box 262, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0110)
    - BD-E AM 15, 14, 1972; 16mm (Box 262, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0111)
    - BD-I, 1972; 16mm (Box 262, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0112)
    - BD-C AM 5-6, 1972; 16mm (Box 262, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0113)
    - BD-D AB-5, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0114)
    - AB-3 (AB-C), 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0115)
    - (AM-11) BD-G, 1972; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0116)
    - BD-I "This was the final attempt", 1972 March 31; 16mm (Box 258, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0117)
    - BD-D (AM 7-8-9h), 1972; 16mm (Box 262, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0118)
    - Drew Assoc Sanford #81 (AM 15, 14th) BD-E, 1972; 16mm (Box 265, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0119)
    - AM-11 BD-G, 1972; 16mm (Box 265, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0120)
    - (AM 1, 2) BD-A, 1972; 16mm (Box 265, Film-reel UA03600001-F16-0121)